Sidney Hillman Foundation Awards Audiovisual Material 6402 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sidney Hillman Foundation Awards Audiovisual Material
2011-2012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sidney Hillman Foundation
6402 AV
2.33 cubic feet
2.1 linear ft.
DVDs.
8819678
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 24, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 11, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6098: Sidney Hillman Foundation Prize for Tom Darcy for His Newsday Cartoons 6098 MB: Sidney Hillman Foundation Banners 6200/004: UNITE HERE Sidney Hillman Foundation Awards 6364: Heather Furnas Collection of Sidney Hillman Foundation Awards Research Materials 6402: Sidney Hillman Foundation Awards
8819678
- Pineros: Men of the Pines/Hector Amezcua -- 2006 Sidney Hillman Awards, 1 (Box 1)
- Hillman Prizes in Journalism: Past Winners, 2009; 1 (Box 2)
- Online Pages - Birth and Death - Carol Guzy, 1 (Box 3)
- Birth and Death/Carol Guzy -- Photojournalism Entry Sidney Hillman Foundation, 1 (Box 4)
- Online Pages - Birth and Death/Carol Guzy [view online with audio], 1 (Box 5)
- Hillman Prize in Journalism Photojournalism -- Below the line: Childhood Poverty on Colorado, 1 (Box 6)
- Hillman Prize in Journalism Photojournalism -- Ian Fisher: American Soldier, 1 (Box 7)
- A Surgery gone wrong. A Life Changed Forever, 1 (Box 8)
- DMN Investigates Bldg, 1 (Box 9)
- A Surgery Gone Wrong. A Life Changed Forever, 1 (Box 10)
- A Surgery Gone Wrong. A Life Changed Forever, 1 (Box 11)
- A Lasting Toll, 1 (Box 12)
- Sidney Hillman Prize for Photojournalism 2013 -- Beyond 7 Billion, 1 (Box 13)
- Sidney Hillman Prize for Photojournalism 2013 -- Beyond 7 Billion, 1 (Box 14)
- Sidney Hillman Prize for Photojournalism 2013 -- Beyond 7 Billion, 1 (Box 15)
- Scout's Honour - Radio Coverage, 1 (Box 16)
- The Fifth Estate -- Scout's Honour -- February 14, 2012, 1 (Box 17)
- The Fifth Estate -- Scout's News Items/National -- February 14, 2012, 1 (Box 18)
- No Running Water Winnipeg Free Press Canadian Hillman Prize 2011, 1 (Box 19)